http://www.mtmckinleybank.com/privacy-policy

Home Disclosures Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy FactsFACTSWHAT DOES MT. McKINLEY BANK DO WITH YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?WHY?Financial companies choose how they share your personal information. Federal law gives consumers the right to limit some but not all sharing. Federal law also requires us to tell you how we collect, share, and protect your personal information. Please read this notice carefully to understand what we do.WHAT?The types of personal information we collect and share depend on the product or service you have with us. This information can include:Social Security number and incomeAccount balances and transaction historyCredit history and Credit ScoresWhen you are no longer our customer, we continue to share your information as described in this notice.HOW?All financial companies need to share customers' personal information to run their everyday business. In the section below, we list the reasons financial companies can share their customers' personal information; the reasons Mt. McKinley Bank chooses to share; and whether you can limit this sharing. Reasons we can share your personal informationReasons we can share your personal informationDoes Mt. McKinley Bank share?Can you limit this sharing?For our everyday business purposes -such as to process your transactions, maintain your account(s), respond to court orders and legal investigations, or report to credit bureausYesNoFor our marketing purposes -to offer our products and services to youYesNoFor joint marketing with other financial companiesNoWe don't share For our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your transactions and experiencesNoWe don’t shareFor our affiliates' everyday business purposes -information about your creditworthinessNoWe don’t shareFor nonaffiliates to market to youNoWe don’t shareQuestions? - Call (907) 452-1751What we doWhat we doHow does Mt. McKinley Bank protect my personal information?To protect your personal information from unauthorized access and use, we use security measures that comply with federal law. These measures include computer safeguards and secured files and buildings.How does Mt. McKinley Bank collect my personal information?We collect your personal information, for example, when youOpen an account or Apply for a loanShow your government-issued ID or give us your contact informationMake deposits or withdrawals from your accountWe also collect your personal information from others, such as credit bureaus or other companies.Why can't I limit all sharing?Federal law gives you the right to limit onlysharing for affiliates' everyday business purposes - information about your creditworthinessaffiliates from using your information to market to yousharing for nonaffiliates to market to youState laws and individual companies may give you additional rights to limit sharing. DefinitionsTermDefinitionAffiliatesCompanies related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Mt. McKinley Bank has no affiliates.Non-affiliatesCompanies not related by common ownership or control. They can be financial and nonfinancial companies.Mt. McKinley Bank does not share with nonaffiliates so they can market to you.Joint MarketingA formal agreement between nonaffiliated financial companies that together market financial products or services to you.Mt. McKinley Bank does not jointly market.
Close
Personal BankingChecking Accounts
Savings Accounts
Retirement Accounts
Consumer Loans
Home Loans
Online & Mobile Banking
Back
Lost or Damaged TokenForgot password or PIN?
